chasingthefrog.com 2008-06-16

# ChasingtheFrog.com PRIVACY POLICY

**ChasingtheFrog.com  
WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY  
**  
The purpose of this notice is to make visitors of ChasingtheFrog.com aware of our commitment to protect their personal information online. We also wish to explain how purchasing works through ChasingtheFrog.com.

**I. Collection of Personal Information  
**The only personal information ChasingtheFrog.com obtains about you is information voluntarily provided by you. This can happen in two ways. 1\. Through e-mail we receive when corresponding with visitors. 2. By posting to our message boards (the online movie forums). This website does not collect additional information about individual visitors from other sources. This means that a person can visit our website and navigate through the website without giving us personal information. To gauge the effectiveness of our website, we may collect non-personal information about our members and visitors, such as Internet server and browser identification, the Internet service provider, clickstream information, the webpage from which a person enters our website, webpages visited at our site, duration of visit and domain type. This information does not reveal a visitor's personal identity.

**II. Use of Personal Information  
**We do not share or disclose your personal information with third parties. We, ChasingtheFrog.com, only use your personal information to add your e-mail address to our newsletter mailing list. To opt out of this list simply reply to our newsletter with the word "remove" in the subject line. We will then delete your name from our database.

**III. Protection of Personal Information  
**We require our staff to protect the privacy of all personal information collected over our website. Only individuals with specific authorization have access to databases containing visitor's personal information. The databases are protected in a secure facility. 

**IV. Purchasing Through ChasingtheFrog.com  
**We offer a large number of items that can be purchased through certain websites who we are in association with. We call these companies that conduct our e-commerce operations and/or order fulfillment "Operational Providers." These four operational providers, listed below, operate independently of ChasingtheFrog.com. When you purchase an item, our Operational Providers will request your personal information to fulfill your order or request. The voluntary submission of your personal information to these Operational Providers, including your order or request, will be governed by the specific provider's terms of usage and privacy policies, which can be found through the links below. We do not share your personal information with our providers nor do they share your personal information with us.

We are in association with the following four sites:

 **·** **[Amazon.com](http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/redirect?tag=chasingthefro-20&path=tg/browse/-/551434)** (privacy and encryption)  
**·** **[MovieGoods, Inc.](http://www.moviegoods.com/privacy_security.asp?&)** (privacy and encryption)   
**·** **[AllPosters.com](http://www.allposters.com/aboutus/privacy.asp)** (privacy and encryption)  
**·** [**Netflix, Inc.**](http://www.netflix.com/PrivacyPolicy) (privacy and encryption)

**V. Notification of Changes in the Privacy Policy  
**We will review our website privacy practices on a periodic basis, and we may modify our policies as we deem appropriate. We may also change or update our website Privacy Policy if we add new services or features and will post these changes in a revised policy available on our website. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy and those of our Operational Providers (see item IV.) on a regular basis.
